<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>day-3</title>
    <link href="/2026/04/07/%E8%AF%81%E4%B9%A6%E8%80%83%E8%AF%95/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%9B%9B%E7%BA%A7/day-3/"/>
    <url>/2026/04/07/%E8%AF%81%E4%B9%A6%E8%80%83%E8%AF%95/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%9B%9B%E7%BA%A7/day-3/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Article 1: Industrial Evolution &amp; Environmental Logic (工业演化与环境逻辑)</p><p>重点涵盖： origin, mill, silicon, transform, cornerstone, presently, utilise, lens, New Hampshire, Bedfordshire, volume, border crossings, maximum, simplicity, recreation, deliberate, cycle, deliver, miracle, major, financial, crisis, disrupt, ecology, inhabitant, hungry, hardship, weigh, merit, safety concerns, spin, out of control, world car-free day, rally, reflect, significant reduction, combat, cloudy, molecule, burn up, raid, organic, lung, branch, ecology, ecology (ecology), ecology (ecology).</p><p>To understand the origin of modern industry, we must look at the mill as the cornerstone of production. However, presently, we utilise a lens of silicon to transform our efficiency. In industrial hubs from New Hampshire to Bedfordshire, the volume of goods at border crossings has reached a maximum. This evolution is anything but a simple recreation; it is a deliberate cycle designed to deliver an economic miracle.</p><p>Yet, every major financial crisis can disrupt the global ecology, leaving the inhabitant hungry and facing hardship. We must weigh the merit of growth against safety concerns, or the system may spin out of control. On World Car-Free Day, a public rally can reflect a significant reduction in pollution, showing our intent to combat a cloudy future. Every molecule of CO2 contributes to the burn up of our atmosphere—a raid on the planet’s lungs. We must protect every branch of the biological organism to survive.</p><p>Article 2: Social Governance &amp; Individual Paths (社会治理与个人路径)</p><p>重点涵盖： discussion, dean, cousin, side by side, determine, abolish, theft, verbal abuse, alley, eager, internship, seize upon, ideal, make a difference, hold fast to, honest, know better, imitate, extremist, post on, post, profile, recruit, speak for, commonplace, article, comprise, parallel, set sail, whale, at sea, absence, integrate into, circle, exchange, catch, crocodile, spot, hopeless, below, level, specialize, extend, advantage, bitter, scare, take it easy, up-to-date, magic, frontier.</p><p>In a recent discussion, a university dean and his cousin sat side by side to determine how to abolish theft and verbal abuse in the city’s dark alleys. They concluded that an eager student in an internship should seize upon an ideal to make a difference. One must hold fast to honest values and know better than to imitate extremist rhetoric.</p><p>This article comprises several parallel arguments: whether we post on social media or a physical post, the profile we recruit must speak for the commonplace citizen. We set sail like a whale at sea, often feeling at sea in the absence of clear guidance. To succeed, one must integrate into a global circle of exchange. If life’s challenges catch you like a crocodile in a tight spot, do not feel hopeless. Even if you are below the expected level, you can specialize to extend your advantage. Don’t let bitter memories scare you; take it easy, stay up-to-date, and find the magic in the new frontier.</p><p>Article 3: Survival, Ethics &amp; Daily Reality (生存、伦理与日常现实)</p><p>重点涵盖： location, Goat Island, lay down, blanket, picturesque, release from, tie, lifetime, fireman, doll, postmaster general, deposit, up to, slender, pale, balloon, implement, clause, restrict, thereby, suicide, turn, inside out, algebra, in short, champagne, affluent, butter, humble, retain, brand, regarding, the Good vehicle, reach, simplicity, by itself, non-life-threatening injuries, plunge, hole over, beat down, inner, album, maximum, record, record (record), record (record).</p><p>At the location of Goat Island, one might lay down a blanket to admire the picturesque view, finally release from the tie of a stressful lifetime. Whether you are a fireman rescuing a doll or a postmaster general securing a deposit, the value of your work is up to your dedication. Even a slender, pale balloon can reflect the fragile beauty of existence.</p><p>To protect this beauty, we must implement every clause to restrict environmental damage, thereby reducing the despair that leads to suicide. Sometimes you must turn your life inside out and solve its problems like a complex algebra equation. In short, whether you are drinking champagne with the affluent or eating butter in a humble cottage, you must retain your personal brand of integrity. Regarding the Good vehicle of social progress, we must reach a level of simplicity where the system mends by itself. Even when facing non-life-threatening injuries, we must plunge into recovery rather than hole over in grief. Do not let the beat down of the world crush your inner spirit; keep your album of memories full of the maximum joy possible.</p><p style="text-align: right; font-size: 1.1em;">  The above articles were written by <strong style="background: linear-gradient(to right, #4285F4, #9B72CB); -webkit-background-clip: text; -webkit-text-fill-color: transparent;">✦ Gemini</strong></p ><p>mention the words and phrase are as follows:<br>album,maximum,beat down,transform,simplicity,implement,by itself,mild,reflect.volume,theft,lay down,blanket,lifetime,dye,recreation,circle,border crossings,financial,empower,burn up,rally,algebra,parallel,utilise,convention,determine,internship,verbal abuse,deposit,imitate,preceding,dean,cousin,side by side,overdue,below,bitter,origin,refine,presently,ballon,crisis,specialize,level,seize upon,at sea,absence,crocodile,mill,plunge,up to,hole over,location,throughout,release from,hardship,hungry,exchange,integrate into,cornerstone,spot,non-life-threatening injuries,honest,slender,suicide,ecology,disrupt,lung,clause,silicon,extend,make a difference,post,picturesque,catch,scare,champagne,major,fireman,doll,Goat island,butter,take it easy,turn,inside out,discussion,ideal,hold fast to,Bedfordshire,deliberate,eager,restrict,solemn,thereby,regarding,know better,safety concerns,pinch,alley,tie,photograph,out of control,whale,speak for,merit,post on,set sail,abolish,inhabitant,significant reduction,affluent,advantage,cloudy,commonplace,combat,extremist,world car-free day,hopeless,anything but,molecule,frontier,spin,civilize,New Hampshire,up-to-date,in short,raid,magic,darling,recruit,profile,postmaster general,retain,organism,lens,the Good vehicle,branch,principle,comprise,brand,miracle,pale,deliver,inner,weigh,article</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>证书考试</category>
      
      <category>英语四级</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>英语四级</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>2026年电视剧观影记录</title>
    <link href="/2026/04/05/%E6%97%A5%E5%B8%B8%E5%A8%B1%E4%B9%90/%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%B3%E4%BD%9C%E5%93%81/2026%E5%B9%B4/2026%E5%B9%B4%E7%94%B5%E8%A7%86%E5%89%A7%E8%A7%82%E5%BD%B1%E8%AE%B0%E5%BD%95/"/>
    <url>/2026/04/05/%E6%97%A5%E5%B8%B8%E5%A8%B1%E4%B9%90/%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%B3%E4%BD%9C%E5%93%81/2026%E5%B9%B4/2026%E5%B9%B4%E7%94%B5%E8%A7%86%E5%89%A7%E8%A7%82%E5%BD%B1%E8%AE%B0%E5%BD%95/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>暂无，等待kiooo808在空闲时间观看一些吧！话说如果能向我推荐一些的话我会不胜感激的！</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>日常娱乐</category>
      
      <category>影音作品</category>
      
      <category>2026年</category>
      
      <category>电视剧观影记录</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>电视剧</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>2026年电影观影记录</title>
    <link href="/2026/04/05/%E6%97%A5%E5%B8%B8%E5%A8%B1%E4%B9%90/%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%B3%E4%BD%9C%E5%93%81/2026%E5%B9%B4/2026%E5%B9%B4%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%A7%82%E5%BD%B1%E8%AE%B0%E5%BD%95/"/>
    <url>/2026/04/05/%E6%97%A5%E5%B8%B8%E5%A8%B1%E4%B9%90/%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%B3%E4%BD%9C%E5%93%81/2026%E5%B9%B4/2026%E5%B9%B4%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%A7%82%E5%BD%B1%E8%AE%B0%E5%BD%95/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>暂无，等待kiooo808在空闲时间观看一些吧！话说如果能向我推荐一些的话我会不胜感激的！</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>日常娱乐</category>
      
      <category>影音作品</category>
      
      <category>2026年</category>
      
      <category>动漫观影记录</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>电影</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>2026年喜爱的音乐</title>
    <link href="/2026/04/05/%E6%97%A5%E5%B8%B8%E5%A8%B1%E4%B9%90/%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%B3%E4%BD%9C%E5%93%81/2026%E5%B9%B4/2026%E5%B9%B4%E5%96%9C%E7%88%B1%E9%9F%B3%E4%B9%90/"/>
    <url>/2026/04/05/%E6%97%A5%E5%B8%B8%E5%A8%B1%E4%B9%90/%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%B3%E4%BD%9C%E5%93%81/2026%E5%B9%B4/2026%E5%B9%B4%E5%96%9C%E7%88%B1%E9%9F%B3%E4%B9%90/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>没关系 -容祖儿🎶<br>我去本人觉得这首歌特别治愈解压好吧。在面临压力或者感到不安的时候，它可以让人内心重归平静。</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>日常娱乐</category>
      
      <category>影音作品</category>
      
      <category>2026年</category>
      
      <category>喜爱的音乐</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>音乐</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>2026年动漫观影记录</title>
    <link href="/2026/04/05/%E6%97%A5%E5%B8%B8%E5%A8%B1%E4%B9%90/%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%B3%E4%BD%9C%E5%93%81/2026%E5%B9%B4/2026%E5%B9%B4%E5%8A%A8%E6%BC%AB%E8%A7%82%E5%BD%B1%E8%AE%B0%E5%BD%95/"/>
    <url>/2026/04/05/%E6%97%A5%E5%B8%B8%E5%A8%B1%E4%B9%90/%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%B3%E4%BD%9C%E5%93%81/2026%E5%B9%B4/2026%E5%B9%B4%E5%8A%A8%E6%BC%AB%E8%A7%82%E5%BD%B1%E8%AE%B0%E5%BD%95/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>四月</strong><br>1.如果能写小说就好了<br>部分情节很鬼畜搞笑就是了。螃蟹公卡哇伊。</p><p>2.正相反的你我<br>甜度爆表！！！没有保持嘴角不上扬的义务！</p><p>3.一起一起这里那里<br>甜呀甜呀ovo</p><p>4.关于完全听不懂老公在说什么的事系列<br>暂未看完qwq</p><p>5.幸运星<br>暂未看完qwq</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>日常娱乐</category>
      
      <category>影音作品</category>
      
      <category>2026年</category>
      
      <category>动漫观影记录</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>动漫</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>读书笔记1</title>
    <link href="/2026/04/05/%E8%AF%BB%E4%B9%A6%E7%AC%94%E8%AE%B0/%E4%BA%BA%E6%96%87%E7%A4%BE%E7%A7%91/%E5%BF%83%E7%90%86%E5%AD%A6/%E4%B8%BA%E4%BD%95%E5%AE%B6%E4%BC%9A%E4%BC%A4%E4%BA%BA/%E8%AF%BB%E4%B9%A6%E7%AC%94%E8%AE%B01/"/>
    <url>/2026/04/05/%E8%AF%BB%E4%B9%A6%E7%AC%94%E8%AE%B0/%E4%BA%BA%E6%96%87%E7%A4%BE%E7%A7%91/%E5%BF%83%E7%90%86%E5%AD%A6/%E4%B8%BA%E4%BD%95%E5%AE%B6%E4%BC%9A%E4%BC%A4%E4%BA%BA/%E8%AF%BB%E4%B9%A6%E7%AC%94%E8%AE%B01/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>我甚至连文章名字都还没想好！静待更新吧！</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>读书笔记</category>
      
      <category>人文社科</category>
      
      <category>心理学</category>
      
      <category>为何家会伤人-武志红</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>原生家庭</tag>
      
      <tag>心理健康</tag>
      
      <tag>沟通</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>day-2</title>
    <link href="/2026/04/05/%E8%AF%81%E4%B9%A6%E8%80%83%E8%AF%95/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%9B%9B%E7%BA%A7/day-2/"/>
    <url>/2026/04/05/%E8%AF%81%E4%B9%A6%E8%80%83%E8%AF%95/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%9B%9B%E7%BA%A7/day-2/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Article 1: The High-Tech Wilderness (荒野中的科技小屋)<br>重点涵盖：random, humble, automate, burn down, centimetre, pair, exhaust, exceed, cycle, idle, beyond doubt, laser, sunset, fancy, arithmetic, virtual, wire, straightforward, intensive, ax, database, famed, fiber, turn on, drawer, fridge, August, uninjured, bundle, supper, sock, hang, bold, turkey, foster, geology, fossil, made up of, rubber, vacation, shall, stove, Saturday, automatic, spray, needle, trash, bush, farm, skin, spring, considerable, peculiar, ward, shape up, desert, bleed, flexible…</p><p>It was a random choice to spend my vacation in the northwest mountains this August. I stayed in a humble cabin made up of rubber, fiber, and concrete. The owner had managed to automate the place; the stove and fridge were automatic, though I had to plug in a wire to turn on the laser security system at sunset. Inside a drawer, I found a bundle of old tools: a needle, an ax, and a pair of socks hanging by the fire. Beside them was a piece of fossil only a few centimetres long. Beyond doubt, the property was famed for its geology. I spent my Saturday doing intensive arithmetic for a database project. The duration was long, but the straightforward task was a remedy for my exhausted mind. I felt like a famed explorer in a virtual world, even though I was simply a fellow looking for peace.</p><p>Article 2: Social Justice &amp; The Guardian (社会正义与卫报)<br>重点涵盖：The Guardian, federal, existing policy, crime, trial, subsidy, council, lobbyist, urge, resign, nasty, current, consensus, reinforce, supervision system, multicultural, mainland, decrease, minor accidents, orchestra, parade, refuse, suitable, following, exploit, struggle, federal, entertain, cause, simply, mean, consumer, characterize, ultimate, triple, captain, distinguish, mainland, humorous, kick around, hold up, scene, far, property, conscientious, circumstance, deem, bill, resign, current, report, council, lobbyist, trust, emphasis, mention, corps, existing policy…</p><p>The Guardian recently issued a report on existing policy regarding federal subsidy plans. The council held a trial to distinguish a suitable remedy from a selfish exploit of the law. A lobbyist tried to urge the captain to resign, calling his refusal to cooperate nasty. However, the current consensus was to reinforce the supervision system to prevent crime. On the mainland, there has been a considerable decrease in minor accidents during the multicultural parade, where a famous orchestra played a triple tune. Even when a clash in the league occurred, the corps was flexible enough to shape up. They would kick around new ideas to entertain the public, but the ultimate decision was to preserve the law and trust the process.</p><p>Article 3: The Confused Creature (惊魂记与意外)<br>重点涵盖：terrify sb. out of sb.’s wits, confused creature, overhear, amuse, torture, scene, geology, conscientious, circumstance, deem, peculiar, ward, obstacle, desert, bleed, nasty, vast, ahead, flexible, suit, appointment, think up, international concern, tune, certainly, chemistry, accent, pregnant, steak, latest, oral, worthy, weaken, motel, or else, northwest, draw on, thermometer, set about, alike, concrete, brilliant blue, conscious, illusion, strike, ugly, mean, simply, drawer, fridge, uninjured, dent, characterize, ultimate, muiticultural (multicultural)…</p><p>A confused creature—a small turkey—wandered into the courtyard, looking ugly and peculiar. I had overheard a rumour that such animals could be nasty. As a conscientious observer, I did not want to torture the bird. However, its sudden strike against the glass was an illusion of safety that terrified me out of my wits. In this circumstance, I had to think up a suitable plan to foster its safety and avoid a scene. The obstacle was its refusal to move toward the bush. Eventually, it became idle near the trash bin. I deemed it uninjured after it stopped bleeding from a small dent on its wing. The ultimate goal was to keep the creature safe until the following morning. It was a spectacular end to a peculiar day.</p><p style="text-align: right; font-size: 1.1em;">  The above articles were written by <strong style="background: linear-gradient(to right, #4285F4, #9B72CB); -webkit-background-clip: text; -webkit-text-fill-color: transparent;">✦ Gemini</strong></p ><p>mention the words and phrase are as follows:<br>random,humble,automate,refusal,selfish,burn down,centimetre,illusion,pair,exhaust,exceed,clash,trial,strike,cycle,idle,beyond doubt,laser,possibly,sunset,ugly,fancy,arithmetic,virtual,wire,straightforward,intensive,ax,database,famed,inform,preserve,urge,present,courtyard,overhear,league,fiber,cause,turn on,drawer,simply,mean,fridge,a supervision system,consumer,August,accustomed,subsidy,uninjured,bundle,quarrel,supper,dent,characterize,sock,parade,ultimate,hang,multicultural,bold,triple,turkey,foster,captain,distinguish,mainland,orchestra,humorous,kick around,geology,hold up,amuse,torture,scene,far,fossil,property,made up of,hyphen,conscientious,own,rubber,circumstance,piece,vacation,shall,stove,criticism,Saturday,deem,confused creature,bill,resign,current,remedy,automatic,spray,spectacular,needle,form,trash,bush,report,decrease,council,lobbyist,trust,emphasis,plug in,duration,normally,mention,farm,skin,spring,considerable,corps,peculiar,ward,shape up,appoint,obstacle,terrify sb. out of sb.’swits,existing policy,desert,bleed,nasty,vast,ahead,flexible,minor accidents,reinforce,fellow,refuse,suitable,following,crime,The guardian,exploit,struggle,federal,entertain</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>证书考试</category>
      
      <category>英语四级</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>英语四级</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>day-1</title>
    <link href="/2026/04/04/%E8%AF%81%E4%B9%A6%E8%80%83%E8%AF%95/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%9B%9B%E7%BA%A7/day-1/"/>
    <url>/2026/04/04/%E8%AF%81%E4%B9%A6%E8%80%83%E8%AF%95/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%9B%9B%E7%BA%A7/day-1/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Article 1: The Collector’s Discovery (古玩店的奇遇)<br>【重点涵盖：】<br>antique, bachelor, beard, chemist, vinegar, strange sight, brilliant blue, glass, yard, orbit, axis, plain, stuff, cord, fairy, torch, specimen, brown patch, frank, mere, genuine, grasp, high-risk, boil over, tackle, compatible, stripe, obvious, cherish, monument.</p><p>【第一部分：意外的发现】<br>I once visited an antique shop in a quiet county. The owner, a bachelor with a long beard, was a chemist by profession but a collector by nature. As I entered, a strange sight caught my eye: a brilliant blue globe sitting on a glass yard table. He explained that it showed the orbit and axis of the Earth.</p><p>【第二部分：实验室的挑战】<br>The shop was plain but filled with stuff: a cord of fairy lights, a torch, and even a specimen of a brown patch butterfly. The owner was frank with me; he said some items were mere copies, but this globe was genuine. I tried to grasp the details, but he warned me it was high-risk to touch. Suddenly, a pot on his stove, filled with vinegar and pepper, began to boil over. He had to overtake the distance to the kitchen to tackle the mess. In his absence, I noticed the globe was compatible with a small stripe on the base. It was obvious he would cherish such a monument to science.</p><p>Article 2: Career and Social Trends (职场与社会趋势)<br>【重点涵盖：】<br>industry, global employment trends, manufacturer, bankrupt, negative, agency, accuse, contempt, nationality, prejudice, in no case, disable, campaigner, initiate, webcast, stimulate, consensus, insight, define, self-sufficient, sympathy, expense, loan, whereas, kneel, quota, insure, lay out, assist, dark, by and by, show up, accordingly, charter, coverage, temporary.</p><p>【第三部分：社会与职场】<br>In today’s industry, global employment trends are changing accordingly. A manufacturer might go bankrupt if they impose too many negative rules. For example, an agency might accuse a manager of contempt if they disapprove of a nationality or show prejudice. In no case should we disable the potential of a temporary worker.</p><p>【第四部分：尾声与细节】<br>A young campaigner decided to initiate a webcast to stimulate a consensus on labor rights. She had the insight to define what a self-sufficient workplace looks like. Her introduction was brilliant. She didn’t show off; instead, she spoke with sympathy for those under the expense of loan debts. Whereas some bosses kneel to profit, she stood for the quota of fairness. To insure success, she had to lay out a plan to assist those in dark times. She knew that by and by, people would show up to support her.</p><p>Article 3: Science and Daily Life (科技、自然与细节)<br>【重点涵盖：】<br>scientific, stream, as follows, petrol, soar, San Francisco, acid, dissolve, layer, poison, particular, nursing, preparation, doctoral, watertight, hazard, bury, stand in, sum, get down to business, presence, escape injury, grateful, twentieth, exhibit, concert, electronic music, feather, drag, vocabulary, suit, appointment, think up, international concern, tune, certainly, chemistry, accent, pregnant, steak, latest, oral, worthy, weaken, motel, or else, northwest, draw on, thermometer, set about, alike, concrete.</p><p>【补充遗漏的零散词汇：】<br>Scientific progress is like a stream; it flows as follows. A chemist in San Francisco found that a certain acid could dissolve a layer of poison. The preparation was worthy of a doctoral study. The lab was watertight to avoid any hazard. The team had to bury their fears and stand in for each other. One night, a rumour spread that petrol prices would soar, increasing their expense sum. They had to get down to business to find a formula (tune).</p><p>Despite the odd presence of a stranger, they remained conscious. In accordance with the charter, they would exhibit their results at the latest by the twentieth. They were grateful to escape injury. The coverage of their success was like a concert of electronic music. Outside, they decided to dump waste in a hole in the northwest. After a long day, they went to a motel to eat a steak and think up new ideas. The thermometer showed it was cold, but their genuine sympathy kept them warm.</p><p style="text-align: right; font-size: 1.1em;">  The above articles were written by <strong style="background: linear-gradient(to right, #4285F4, #9B72CB); -webkit-background-clip: text; -webkit-text-fill-color: transparent;">✦ Gemini</strong></p ><p>mention the words and phrase are as follows:<br>petrol,soar,prejudice,polish,wheel,accordingly,insure,particular,as follows,loose,high-risk,erect,cover for,pepper,axis,intimate,by and by,attract,agency,cord,bachelor,accuse,a brown patch,boil over,in no case,odd,nursing,pose,specimen,behind the scenes,show up,plain,overtake,beard,twentieth,compatible,carry off,in store,go through,hole,exhibit,san francisco,earthy,dump,obvious,industry,stream,antique,yard,impose,tackle,webcast,glass,cherish,fair,grasp,initiate,stuff,concert,preparation,torch,stranger,keep from,layer,by nature,rumour,accordance,get down to business,charter,mere,coverage,contempt,negative,harbour,assist,nationality,scientific,temporary,electronic music,feather,drag,vocabulary,define,acid,escape injury,bankrupt,self-sufficient,county,manufacturer,asleep,frank,stand in,suit,loan,appointment,think up,sympathy,international concern,tune,stimulate,presence,consensus,certainly,chemistry,accent,stripe,vinegar,pregnant,a strange sight,monument,poison,steak,grateful,orbit,treat,dissolve,patch,doctoral,at the latest,lay out,dark,watertight,fairy,oral,hazard,worthy,weaken,motel,campaigner,chemist,whereas,or else,kneel,quota,expense,sum,insight,disable,bury,northwest,show off,draw on,genuine,thermometer,set about,introduction,disapprove,global employment trends,alike,concrete,brilliant blue,conscious</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>证书考试</category>
      
      <category>英语四级</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>英语四级</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>自恋使人困身孤岛</title>
    <link href="/2026/04/03/%E4%B8%AA%E4%BA%BA%E5%86%99%E4%BD%9C/%E8%87%AA%E6%81%8B%E4%BD%BF%E4%BA%BA%E5%9B%B0%E8%BA%AB%E5%AD%A4%E5%B2%9B/"/>
    <url>/2026/04/03/%E4%B8%AA%E4%BA%BA%E5%86%99%E4%BD%9C/%E8%87%AA%E6%81%8B%E4%BD%BF%E4%BA%BA%E5%9B%B0%E8%BA%AB%E5%AD%A4%E5%B2%9B/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>  自恋是天生的！<br>呃呃呃暂时没时间写，等待更新吧…  </p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>个人写作</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>性格分析</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>电子技术</title>
    <link href="/2026/04/03/%E5%AD%A6%E6%A0%A1%E8%AF%BE%E7%A8%8B/%E7%94%B5%E5%AD%90%E6%8A%80%E6%9C%AF/%E7%94%B5%E5%AD%90%E6%8A%80%E6%9C%AF/"/>
    <url>/2026/04/03/%E5%AD%A6%E6%A0%A1%E8%AF%BE%E7%A8%8B/%E7%94%B5%E5%AD%90%E6%8A%80%E6%9C%AF/%E7%94%B5%E5%AD%90%E6%8A%80%E6%9C%AF/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>此项课程为大一下的课程，仅以复习为目的整理发布。如有侵权，请联系删除。</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>学校课程</category>
      
      <category>电子技术</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>专业课</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>电气控制技术</title>
    <link href="/2026/04/03/%E5%AD%A6%E6%A0%A1%E8%AF%BE%E7%A8%8B/%E7%94%B5%E6%B0%94%E6%8E%A7%E5%88%B6%E6%8A%80%E6%9C%AF/%E7%94%B5%E6%B0%94%E6%8E%A7%E5%88%B6%E6%8A%80%E6%9C%AF/"/>
    <url>/2026/04/03/%E5%AD%A6%E6%A0%A1%E8%AF%BE%E7%A8%8B/%E7%94%B5%E6%B0%94%E6%8E%A7%E5%88%B6%E6%8A%80%E6%9C%AF/%E7%94%B5%E6%B0%94%E6%8E%A7%E5%88%B6%E6%8A%80%E6%9C%AF/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>此项课程为大一下的课程，仅以复习为目的整理发布。如有侵权，请联系删除。</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>学校课程</category>
      
      <category>电气控制技术</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>专业课</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>机械制图</title>
    <link href="/2026/04/03/%E5%AD%A6%E6%A0%A1%E8%AF%BE%E7%A8%8B/%E6%9C%BA%E6%A2%B0%E5%88%B6%E5%9B%BE/%E6%9C%BA%E6%A2%B0%E5%88%B6%E5%9B%BE/"/>
    <url>/2026/04/03/%E5%AD%A6%E6%A0%A1%E8%AF%BE%E7%A8%8B/%E6%9C%BA%E6%A2%B0%E5%88%B6%E5%9B%BE/%E6%9C%BA%E6%A2%B0%E5%88%B6%E5%9B%BE/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>此项课程为大一上的课程，现已结课。仅以复习为目的整理发布。如有侵权，请联系删除。</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>学校课程</category>
      
      <category>机械制图</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>专业课</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>信息技术</title>
    <link href="/2026/04/03/%E5%AD%A6%E6%A0%A1%E8%AF%BE%E7%A8%8B/%E4%BF%A1%E6%81%AF%E6%8A%80%E6%9C%AF/%E4%BF%A1%E6%81%AF%E6%8A%80%E6%9C%AF/"/>
    <url>/2026/04/03/%E5%AD%A6%E6%A0%A1%E8%AF%BE%E7%A8%8B/%E4%BF%A1%E6%81%AF%E6%8A%80%E6%9C%AF/%E4%BF%A1%E6%81%AF%E6%8A%80%E6%9C%AF/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>此项课程为大一上的课程，现已结课。仅以复习为目的整理发布。如有侵权，请联系删除。</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>学校课程</category>
      
      <category>信息技术</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>专业课</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>电机及拖动基础</title>
    <link href="/2026/04/03/%E5%AD%A6%E6%A0%A1%E8%AF%BE%E7%A8%8B/%E7%94%B5%E6%9C%BA%E5%8F%8A%E6%8B%96%E5%8A%A8%E5%9F%BA%E7%A1%80/%E7%94%B5%E6%9C%BA%E5%8F%8A%E6%8B%96%E5%8A%A8%E5%9F%BA%E7%A1%80/"/>
    <url>/2026/04/03/%E5%AD%A6%E6%A0%A1%E8%AF%BE%E7%A8%8B/%E7%94%B5%E6%9C%BA%E5%8F%8A%E6%8B%96%E5%8A%A8%E5%9F%BA%E7%A1%80/%E7%94%B5%E6%9C%BA%E5%8F%8A%E6%8B%96%E5%8A%A8%E5%9F%BA%E7%A1%80/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>此项课程为大一下的课程，仅以复习为目的整理发布。如有侵权，请联系删除。</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>学校课程</category>
      
      <category>电机及拖动基础</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>专业课</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>电路基础</title>
    <link href="/2026/04/03/%E5%AD%A6%E6%A0%A1%E8%AF%BE%E7%A8%8B/%E7%94%B5%E8%B7%AF%E5%9F%BA%E7%A1%80/%E7%94%B5%E8%B7%AF%E5%9F%BA%E7%A1%80/"/>
    <url>/2026/04/03/%E5%AD%A6%E6%A0%A1%E8%AF%BE%E7%A8%8B/%E7%94%B5%E8%B7%AF%E5%9F%BA%E7%A1%80/%E7%94%B5%E8%B7%AF%E5%9F%BA%E7%A1%80/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>此项课程为大一上的课程，现已结课。仅以复习为目的整理发布。如有侵权，请联系删除。</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>学校课程</category>
      
      <category>电路基础</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>专业课</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>自我与关系边界</title>
    <link href="/2026/04/02/%E4%B8%AA%E4%BA%BA%E5%86%99%E4%BD%9C/%E8%87%AA%E6%88%91%E4%B8%8E%E5%85%B3%E7%B3%BB%E8%BE%B9%E7%95%8C/"/>
    <url>/2026/04/02/%E4%B8%AA%E4%BA%BA%E5%86%99%E4%BD%9C/%E8%87%AA%E6%88%91%E4%B8%8E%E5%85%B3%E7%B3%BB%E8%BE%B9%E7%95%8C/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>  在与女友闹掰的那个夜晚，我做了一个很舒服的梦，梦里我帮一个女孩脱离了困境。<br>  现实，当我在聊天界面上看见那条纯表情消息。我内心很煎熬，为什么她这么冷漠呢。我做错什么了么，我觉得有做错事情的地方都已经考虑到并在这之前解释了呀。反复的看手机，希望她继续发消息说明一下，不然我自己猜的话什么情况都有可能的呀。好纠结呀，我现在应该说什么呢。编辑好消息又删掉，怎么她还不发消息呢。唉算了，我还是直接问吧！我去，又回我表情是什么鬼。我有这么让她生气吗。哎呀这种情况该咋办呢。要是能面对面交流就好了，起码能看见对方的表情和态度。好纠结呀。。。好吧，既然你不想理我那我也不理你吧！咱们是俩小孩吗，唉。太冷漠了吧。。。我去，她似乎心情不太好。但是她又不给我说发生了什么，我根本不知道该咋回应怎么办。好吧，那心情不好对我冷淡也可以理解吧。欸不对呀，我怎么感觉她在通过冷漠对我散发怨气呢。唉我都说了很多次不要这样说话只说一半，真让人着急呀。这样的话我就只能受着这股负面情绪了呀，但是我们如果沟通的话就会好很多的。为什么总是记不住呢唉。算了吧，如果是这样的话我就不理她了。呵呵呵自己的女朋友怎么可能视而不见呢，但是我只能干着急呀。唉，好绝望。突然感觉好累是什么鬼。一点也不信任我，好吧！很气愤，我都不知道怎么在心里辩解她没有不信任我了。唉，好压抑。好焦虑，好绝望，以后也总要这样吗，感觉跟幸福生活不搭边啊。唉，鸭梨山大。<br>  梦里，帮助了一个女孩，很活泼可爱。其实我只是做了一个举动就帮助了她，最后她还告诉我了她的名字。梦很短，但是醒来就记不清了，名字也一同忘记了，印象中只觉得是一个很好听的名字。<br>  现实和梦境是如此矛盾。<br>  所以我睡醒后第一时间竟然有些错愕，为什么昨晚明明那么伤心，却做了这么轻松的梦而感到神清气爽呢。想着想着终于自觉不足，意识到其实自己一直是一个没有边界感的人。如果我的快乐只能建立在别人的不冷漠之上，那我还是我吗？我根本就没有维护好自我与外界的边界，所以才会以他人的反应来确认我的自我，把自己变成了一个反射他人行为的镜子。虽然这证明我的喜怒哀乐不是我产生的，但是我到底是在关心她还是在通过她的回应来确认我的存在感呢？我太自私了，其实那时的着急更多的是因为我自己无法处理那个不被回应的自我。要想拥有真正的自我应该首先做到分清界限，明白自我与他人的边界。其次就是要独立，不应该依附在他人身上。我还需要慢慢改正…话说还要多久才能成为一个圆呢？希望我们所拥有的关系都可以顺利度过1+1&#x3D;1，1+1&#x3D;0两个阶段，成功到达1+1&#x3D;2的阶段吧！</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>个人写作</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>自我边界</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
